//Object containing questions, answers, and commonly used variables
const myQUIZ = [
    //1
{
  question: "Who is the wife of Hades?",
  answerOptions: [
        "Persephone",
        "Demeter",
        "Aphrodite",
        "Hestia"
        ],
  correctAnswer: "Persephone"
    },
    //2
{
  question: "What is the name of the river that flows through the Greek Underworld?",
  answerOptions: [
      "Ladon",
      "Styx",
      "Kladeos",
      "Charon"
      ],
  correctAnswer: "Styx"
    },
    //3
{
  question: "Which of the following is not one of Zeus' children?",
  answerOptions: [
      "Ares",
      "Pollux",
      "Pandora",
      "Orion"
      ],
  correctAnswer: "Pandora"
    },
    //4
{
  question: "Which of the following creatures did Hercules/Heracles not slay?",
  answerOptions: [
      "The Nemean Lion",
      "Nessus the Centaur",
      "The Hydra of Lerna",
      "The Arcadian Stag"
      ],
  correctAnswer: "The Arcadian Stag"
    },
    //5
{
  question: "What river was Achilles dipped in to grant him invulnerability?",
  answerOptions: [
      "Ladon",
      "Styx",
      "Kladeos",
      "Charon"
      ],
  correctAnswer: "Styx"
    },
    //6
{
  question: "After accidentally seeing Artemis bathing, Actaeon was transformed into what animal?",
  answerOptions: [
      "Swan",
      "Horse",
      "Boar",
      "Stag"
      ],
  correctAnswer: "Stag"
    },
    //7
{
  question: "How was Aphrodite born?",
  answerOptions: [
      "She sprung from the head of her father",
      "She was born from the castrated genitals of Uranus",
      "She was shaped and molded from gold",
      "She burst from the flayed carcass of the Erymathian Boar"
      ],
  correctAnswer: "She was born from the castrated genitals of Uranus"
    },
    //8
{
  question: "What is Dionysus the god of?",
  answerOptions: [
      "Joy & Family",
      "Wine & Parties",
      "Nature & Balance",
      "Vengeance & Wrath"
      ],
  correctAnswer: "Wine & Parties"
    },
    //9
{
  question: "Charybdis, the sea monster, was rationalized as actually being a:",
  answerOptions: [
      "Whirlpool",
      "Hurricane",
      "Lightning Storm",
      "Tidal Wave"
      ],
  correctAnswer: "Whirlpool"
    },
    //10
{
  question: "Who built the Labyrinth of Crete, which contained the Minotaur?",
  answerOptions: [
      "Icarus",
      "Hephaestus",
      "Daedalus",
      "Archimedes"
      ],
  correctAnswer: "Daedalus"
    }
];